Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 3: Committees, 1912-1993; 10 boxes
  - Miscellaneous Committees, 1960-1977; 1 box
    - Trustees' Committee on Student Life, Health and Athletics, 1968-1972; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 14)
      [restricted until 2022]
    - Rules and Rights Committee - Judicial Committee, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Rights and Rules Committee, 1962-1968; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Subcommittee on Athletic Eligibility, 1954-1973; 1 box
    - Faculty Committee on Athletic Eligibility, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Student Athletic Eligibility Cards, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1957-1958; 1 box (Box 57)
    - Minutes, 1954-1957; 1 box (Box 57)
  - Residence Committee, 1973-1984; 1 box
    - Residence Committee - Minutes, Etc, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Residence Committee - Minutes, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Residence Committee - Minutes, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Residence Committee, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Residence Committee - Miscellaneous Papers, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Residence Committee, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Residence Committee Meetings, Spring, 1976; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Residence Committee, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Residence Committee, Daily Princetonian Articles, 1975; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Office of Physical Planning, 1973; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Residence Committee Material, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Indirect Cost Policies, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee on Policy and the President, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Series 4: Residential Advisors, 1965-2000; 13 boxes; 2 folders; 2 items
  The Residential Advisors series contains records which document the Dean of Students' oversight of residential college advisor programs. Included are records pertaining to residential advisors, minority affairs advisors, and the freshman summer orientation program. Included are applications for positions, lists of advisors, correspondence, and student questionnaires gauging the success of these programs.
  The arrangement of the records at the time of transfer has been retained. Applications for residential advisor positions are grouped chronologically.
  Records in Series 4: Residential Advisors are closed for a period of 75 years, or if pertaining to individuals, until the individual's death.
  - Residential Advisor Information - Memos, Correspondence, Lists, Etc., 1971-1975; 1 box
    - 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 1972-1973, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 1971-1972, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Advisee Groups and Sophomore Group Names, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - List of Advisors, 1970-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Resident Advisor Lists, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Selection Process Materials, 1971-1975; 1 box
    - List of Applicants, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Rank of Applicants, 1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Selection for Spring '74, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Applicant List, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Interview Committee Material, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Frosh Questionnaire, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Questionnaires, 1972; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Questionnaires, 1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Board of Advisors, 1972-1975; 1 box
    - 1974-1975, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - 1972-1974, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Meetings at Counseling Center, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Freshmen-Faculty Discussion Reports and Residential Advisor Requests, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Freshmen-Faculty Discussion Groups during Freshmen Week, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Wilson College Residential Advisor Meetings, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Individual Meetings with Residential Advisors (Small Group Meetings), 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Small Group Meetings, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Housing History, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Room Selection, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Orientations, 1972-1976; 1 box
    - Summer and Freshmen Week, 1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Materials, Fall, 1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Blairstown, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Retreat, 1973; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Packet, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Fall, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Blairstown Evaluations, 1974 April-1975 September; 1 box
      - 1975 September, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - 1974 April, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Alternate Selection at Wilson College - Correspondence with Sekazi Mtingwa and H. Drewry, Spring, 1975; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Referral Letters from Department Heads, 1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Director of Residential Advisors, 1970; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Interviews, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Residential Fellows Correspondence, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Resident Fellows Program List, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Advisors Correspondence and Lists, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Residential Fellows Correspondence and Lists, 1968-1970; 1 box
    - 1969-1970, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - 1968-1969, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Brown Hall Program / Publicity, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Job Description of Resident Advisor Position, 1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Current List, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - History of the Program, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - "How to Set Up a Residential Advisor Program,", 1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Reports on Fall Recess, 1972; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - Selection Rankings, 1973; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Female Residential Advisors, 1973-1974; 1 box
    - Cross, Mary GS (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Friedman, Judith '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Garber, Mary Deb '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Handel, Shelley GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Kristof, Patricia '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Margan, Michelle '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Muenzer, Susan '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Rothenberg, Karen GS (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Schultze, Christine '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Takeuchi, Vicki '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Thuan, Trinh Xuan GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Tropp, Barbara GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Wasserheit, Judy '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Wizowaty, Suzi '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - McIntyre, Joy '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Kerrigan, Joan GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Male Residential Advisors, 1973-1974; 1 box
    - Atkinson, Paul C '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Bhalla, Surjit GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Collins, Leonard GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Arch GS (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Farkas, Charlie (Chuck) '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Foellinger, David '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Frist, William (Bill) '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - George, David Lloyd '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Harper, Blanton '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Kimberly, Michael GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Krishnan, Mohadevan GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Lesh, William '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Lytle, James '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Mohan, Rakesh GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Mowrey, Rob '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Obermann, Dick GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - O'Neill, Hugh '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Shifferd, Dave '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Smith, David A '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Spitalnik, Steven '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Stull, Owen '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Tweardy, David '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Wymes, Michael '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Zisler, Randy GS (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Alternate Residential Advisors, 1973-1974; 1 box
    - Rinaldini, Louis '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Eitches, Robert '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Weil, Stephen '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Issues with Residential Advisors, 1972-1973; 1 box
    - Boraas, Marcia '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Harris, J Elizabeth '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Kirkpatrick, Melanie '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Leff, Deborah '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - Machlowitz, Marilyn M '74 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Messina, Maria '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - Sachs, Harriet '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - Stieg, Laura '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - Upshaw, Carolyn '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 53)
    - Watson, Laurie '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 54)
    - Wright, Lorna '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - Alternate Women, 1972-1973; 1 box
    - Bernstein, Ellen '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - Eure, Dianna '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 57)
    - Schlachter, Marylin '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 58)
    - Shorter, Dori L '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 59)
  - Alternates, 1972-1973; 1 box
    - Dobel, Patrick GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - Burns, Kevin '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - Maszak, Andrew S GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - Szubski, John GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 63)
    - Beller, David GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 64)
    - Berg, Barry '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 65)
    - Carples, Jeffrey '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 66)
    - Carroll, Richard '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 67)
    - Comer, Wayne '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 68)
    - Dobel, Patrick GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 69)
    - Ducibella, Tom GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 70)
    - Dugger, Edward III, GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 71)
    - Edwards, Hannibal '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 72)
    - Ephros, Moshe '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 73)
    - Frohman, Daniel '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 74)
    - GAeln, Frantisek GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 75)
    - Hartnett, Alex '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 76)
    - Herron, Waddell '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 77)
    - Joseph, Peter '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 78)
    - Keslar, William '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 79)
    - Kimberley, Michael GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 80)
    - King, Eric Stephen GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 81)
    - Klaus, David GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 82)
    - Lecky, James P. '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 83)
    - Linowes, Richard '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 84)
    - McCullough, Wayne '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 85)
    - Marchese, Joseph GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 86)
    - Oberman, Dick GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 87)
    - Paschal, R. Wade Jr. '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 88)
    - Piskun, Andrew '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 89)
    - Schuster, Mr./Mrs. John/Belinda (Housing), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 90)
    - Selligman, Scott '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 91)
    - Smith, K. L. '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 92)
    - Sweeny, Paul E. '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 93)
    - Tomberlin, George GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 94)
    - Zeitzoff, Peter GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 95)
  - Surveys, Applications, Recommendations, 1971-1972; 1 box
    - Anderson, Grant W. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 96)
    - Banisch, Francis '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 97)
    - Arbogast, Stephen GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 98)
    - Bennette, Jim and Karen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 99)
    - Brightenback, Kristine, GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 100)
    - Callison, John, '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 101)
    - Case, Duncan GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 102)
    - D'Acquisto, Robert '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 103)
    - Duffy, Angenette '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 104)
    - Etlin, Richard and Melissa, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 105)
    - Floden, Bob '71, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 106)
    - Hartman, Ronald, '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 107)
    - Gibson, Mary GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 108)
    - Herman, Robin '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 109)
    - Kelikian, Alice '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 110)
    - Latella, John '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 111)
    - Levy, Marsha '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 112)
    - Lloyd, Pamela '73, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 113)
    - Madden, Theodore '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 114)
    - Matthews, Jenny, '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 115)
    - Maurrer, Steven GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 116)
    - Marzouk, Joseph '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 117)
    - Miller, Corbin '71, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 118)
    - Mito, Robert '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 119)
    - Fehsenfeld, Robert Jr. '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 120)
    - Ochshorn, Peter '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 121)
    - Page, Michele 72', dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 122)
    - Pedersen, Neil '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 123)
    - Penick, Henry L. '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 124)
    - Pritchard, James L. '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 125)
    - Reepmeyer, Thomas '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 126)
    - Sease, Ann '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 127)
    - Semida, John '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 128)
    - Strauss, Deborah '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 129)
    - Staton, Romulus '71, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 130)
    - Thomas, Joseph Thomas GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 131)
    - Tropp, Barbara GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 132)
    - Varma, Ashok GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 133)
    - Vy, Ban '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 134)
    - White, Charles '72, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 135)
    - Miller, Judith GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 136)
    - Deknis, Edward GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 137)
    - Minyard, Rosemary GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 138)
    - Weiss, T. (Issues), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 139)
    - MacGregor, John Monroe GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 140)
  - Residential Advisors, 1970-1971; 1 box
    - Lists, Correspondence, Etc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 141)
    - Letters of Acceptance, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 142)
    - Women - Yes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 143)
    - Undergrad Men - Yes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 144)
    - Grad Men - Yes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 145)
    - Couples - Yes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 146)
    - Waiting List, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 147)
  - Residential Fellows, 1967-1970; 1 box
    - Accepted, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 148)
    - 1968-1969, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 149)
    - Alts, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 150)
  - Residential Advisors, 1974-1975; 1 box
    - Austin, Vanessa D. '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Backer, Jo Rachel '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Bayer, Bill '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Block, Robin '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Brean, Rich '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Britton, Della '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Csete, Marie E. '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Csicsery-Ronay, Istvan GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Devarajan, Shantayanan '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Domb, Martin '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Enrich, Peter and Peggy GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Felsher, Celia '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Franklin, Evangeline '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Gallos, Joan '73 (Admin), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Hakimi, Farokh S. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Hardorp, Detlef GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Iwens, Judy Lynn '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Johnston, Kathreen '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Kornfeld, Howard John '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Lam, Eva '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Levinson, Jules '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Link, Perry (Faculty), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - McQuarter, Gregory GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Naficy, Anahita '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Neubert, Nancy '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Pettit, Peter '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Perles, Suzanne '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Philip, Craig E. '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Pomar, Joseph J. '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Quon, Tony GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Robie, Marilyn B. '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Rothschild, Anthony '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Sauthoff, Ned R. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Silverman, Debbie '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Silvert, Donald '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Joel David '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Soffer, Lynn '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Swigert, James '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Vaughn, Lea '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Wartenburg, Carl and Karen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Zevin, Wendy '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Advisees, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Residential Advisors (Withdrawals), 1974-1975; 1 box
    - Meyer, Burglind L, Assistant Master (Applicant), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Reeves, Randy and May, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Scott, Deborah '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Gascoigne, John GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Cox, Thomas GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Serwer, Daniel and Jacqueline GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Norton, Robert and Wendy GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Residential Advisors (Alternates), dates not examined; 1 box
    - Bisnow, Mark C. GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Bradley, Kathleen '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Davy, Kent GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Soppas, Despina '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Peek, Gail Asst. Master (Applicant), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Loebl, Judith '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Lee, William '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Munenzer, Genevieve '75, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Ward, Wanda '76, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 58)
  - Residential Advisors, 1976-1977; 1 box
    - Bass, Cheryl A. '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Castle, June '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Burroughs, David '78, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Chun, Cornell GS (Unsuccessfully Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Connolly, John (Chris) '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Erickson, Mark Harley '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Feder, Judith '78 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Felzenberg, Al GS, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Foote, Tamasin '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Frye, Rose Jeanette '77, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Gilbert, Robert DeWitt '77 (Reapplied), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 11)